Privacy Policy

Effective date: 31 March 2022

This is the privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") for information collected by GV Management

Company, L.L.C. or GV UK Management Company Limited (together “GV”) and for

https://www.gv.com/ ("Site"). The Site is operated by or on behalf of GV.

Our Privacy Policy explains:

● What information we collect and why we collect it.

● How we use that information.

● The choices we offer, including how to access and update information.

We’ve tried to keep this Privacy Policy as simple as possible but if you have any questions,

please feel free to contact us at privacy@gv.com.

Information that we collect

We collect information to provide better services to all those with whom we deal.

We collect information in the following ways:

● Information you give us. For example, information that you provide to us when

contacting us for inquiries about potential investment or other commercial opportunities,

employment details if you send us a CV, resumé or other details of your employment

history in connection with an advertised job vacancy or a general enquiry regarding

employment opportunities with us. When you do, we may ask for personal information

like your name, email address, telephone number and other details.

● Information we collect or receive in the course of our investment business. We

may receive or collect personal information in the course of our investment activities,

such as when researching potential investment opportunities or in conducting our legal

and commercial due diligence. This could include, for example, information about the

management and other personnel at a company we may be assessing an investment in.

● Information we get from your use of our Site. We may collect information about the

parts of the Site that you use and how you use it. This information includes:

○ Device information

We may collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model,

operating system version, unique device identifiers, and mobile network

information including phone number).

○ Log information

When you use our Site, we may automatically collect and store certain

information in server logs. This may include:

● details of how you used our Site;● Internet protocol address;● device event information, such as crashes, system activity, hardware

settings, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your

request and referral URL; and/or● cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.

○ Location information

We may collect and process information about your actual location and use

various technologies to determine location, including IP address.

○ Local storage

We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on

your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5)

and application data caches.

○ Cookies and similar technologies

We may use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit

our Site, and this may include using cookies or similar technologies to identify

your browser or device. You may set your browser to block all cookies, including

cookies associated with this Site or to indicate when a cookie is being set by us.

How we use information that we collect

We use personal information to manage and operate our business, including to explore new

investment opportunities, manage our existing portfolio, develop and maintain our contacts and

recruit staff. Where necessary, we may also use personal information to protect the interests of

GV, our employees and affiliates (for example in the event of a legal claim).

When you contact us, we keep a record of your communication to help solve any issues you

might be facing. We may use your email address to inform you about our business, such as

letting you know about upcoming events or changes to our business.

We use the information we collect from our Site to provide, maintain, protect and improve it and

to protect our users. We may use information collected from cookies and other technologies to

improve your user experience and the overall quality of our Site.

Our legal basis for processing your personal information

If UK data protection law applies to our processing of your personal information, it is important

that you know the lawful basis on which we process your personal information.

We rely on the following legal basis, under UK data protection law, to process your personal

data:

● Where we have obtained your consent, for example to action a request from you or

respond to your specific query. You can withdraw your consent at any time, but we may

still need to retain a record of your correspondence with us.

● Where it is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests to manage our existing

investments and explore new investment opportunities, including conducting legal and

commercial due diligence.

● Where it is necessary to comply with a legal obligation, for example under anti-money

laundering or anti-bribery legislation.

Transfer of personal information

GV is headquartered in the US, with an office in the UK. Consequently, any information we

collect will be transferred to, and stored in, the US and other countries where the data protection

laws may offer a lower standard of protection than in your country of residence. Where personal

information is transferred outside the UK, we will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure

that it is subject to appropriate safeguards and that it is treated securely and in accordance with

this Privacy Policy.

Adhesion to the Privacy Shield Frameworks

GV Management Company, L.L.C. has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it

adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. We comply with the EU-U.S and Swiss-US Privacy

Shield Frameworks as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection,

use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union, United

Kingdom and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. If there is any conflict between the

terms in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles

shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, and to view our certification,

please visit https://www.privacyshield.gov/.

Accountability for onward transfers

We are responsible and remain liable for the processing of personal information we receive,

under the Privacy Shield Frameworks, including if we subsequently transfer to a third party

acting as an agent on its behalf. We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward

transfers of personal information from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer

liability provisions.

With respect to personal information received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield

Frameworks, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade

Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal information in

response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law

enforcement requirements.

Resolution of Privacy Shield queries and complaint mechanism

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about our

collection or use of your personal information. European Economic Area and Swiss individuals

with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact us at

privacy@gv.com.

We have further committed to refer unresolved Privacy Shield complaints to JAMS. If you do not

receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint from us, or if we have not resolved your

complaint, please contact or visit https://www.jamsadr.com/eu-us-privacy-shield or to file a

complaint visit https://www.jamsadr.com/file-an-eu-us-privacy-shield-or-safe-harbor-claim. The

services of JAMS are provided at no cost to you. As further explained in the Privacy Shield

Principles, a binding arbitration option may also be made available to you in order to address

residual complaints not resolved by any other means.

We commit to cooperate with the EU DPA panel established by the EU data protection

authorities ("EU DPA panel") and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information

Commissioner (as applicable) and to comply with the advice given such EU DPA panel and/or

the Swiss Commissioner (as applicable) with regard to human resources data transferred from

the EU DPA and/or Switzerland to GV Management Company, L.L.C. in the context of the

employment relationship.

Enforcement

GV is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade

Commission. GV may be required to share your personal information, including the disclosure

of EU and Swiss personal information, to public authorities and law enforcement agencies in

response to lawful requests, including requests to meet national security and law enforcement

requirements.

Right to access, update and delete your personal information

If you are a resident of California or the UK and/or your personal information is processed in

the context of our UK office, you have certain legal rights in respect of the personal information

about you held by us, including, for California residents, your rights under the California

Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA). This includes the right to obtain a copy of this information on

request, and the right to correct, amend or delete such personal information or object to it being

used for certain purposes (including marketing). We may ask you to verify your identity before

we can act on your request.

We will comply with any requests to exercise your rights in accordance with applicable law, and

so there may be circumstances where we are entitled to refuse your request. For example,

where permitted to by law, we may reject requests that are unreasonably repetitive, require

disproportionate technical effort (for example, developing a new system or fundamentally

changing an existing practice), risk the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for

instance, requests concerning information residing on backup systems).

Where we can provide information access and correction, we will do so free of charge, except

where it would require a disproportionate effort (where we are permitted to charge a fee under

applicable law). We aim to maintain any information we hold and our Site in a manner that

protects information from accidental or malicious destruction.

To make any requests regarding your personal information, or if you have any questions or

concerns regarding your personal information, you should contact us at privacy@gv.com. You

are also entitled to contact your local supervisory authority for data protection. In the UK, the

data protection authority is the Information Commissioner’s Office.

Right to object

You have the right to object (opt-out) of your personal information being used for purposes

which are materially different to the purposes for which it was collected, as described in this

Privacy Policy (including being disclosed to a third party). We may refuse your request where

we have a right to do so (for example, if the use is necessary to comply with a legal obligation).

To exercise any of your rights, please contact us at privacy@gv.com

Information that we share

We do not sell your personal information. We share personal information with companies,

organisations and individuals outside of GV in the following circumstances:

● With your consent

We may share personal information with companies, organisations or individuals outside

GV when we have your consent to do so.

● For external processing

We provide personal information to our affiliates or other trusted businesses or persons

to process it for us or for similar reasons (for example, in connection with using shared

compute resources and servers), based on our instructions and in compliance with our

Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

● With our legal and professional advisors

We share information with our legal and other professional advisors, for example if they

are advising us on an investment transaction or where otherwise necessary to obtain

their advice.

● For legal reasons

We may share personal information with companies, organisations or individuals outside

GV if we have a belief in good faith that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the

information is reasonably necessary to:

● meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable

governmental request;

● enforce applicable terms of service, including investigation of potential

violations;● detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues;

and/or● protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of GV, our users or

the public, as required or permitted by law.

If GV is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale of GV, we will use reasonable

endeavours to ensure the personal information we process continues to be subject to the same

protections set out in this Privacy Policy.

Information security

We work hard to protect our Site and any information that we hold from unauthorized access or

unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction. In particular:

● We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including

physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.

● We restrict access to personal information to GV employees, contractors, service

providers and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for

us and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations. They may

be disciplined or their contract terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

When this Privacy Policy applies

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered and businesses operated by GV, but

excludes services and businesses that have separate privacy policies that do not incorporate

this Privacy Policy.

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered or businesses operated by other

companies or individuals. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other

companies and organisations that advertise our services and that may use cookies, pixel tags

and other technologies.

Changes

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on

this page and, if deemed necessary, we will provide a more prominent notice.

Contacting us

Please submit any questions, concerns or comments you have about this Privacy Policy or any

requests concerning your personal information by email to privacy@gv.com.

For the purposes of UK data protection law, GV UK Management Limited is the data controller

of your personal information. Our address in the UK is 146-148 Clerkenwell Road, London,

EC1R 5DG.
